yonex.com 2016-11-19

# YONEX - world leader in Golf, Tennis and Badminton

  * You are here:
  * Home
  * Company
  * Privacy Policy 

## Personal information

At YONEX, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit YONEX on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need - to correspond with you, or provide you with a subscription, for example - it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it.

We have implemented these practices for the YONEX Web site ([www.YONEX.com](http://www.yonex.com/)). We are also instructing our employees around the world to include information on privacy practices everywhere information is collected on the YONEX Web, tailored to what that portion of the site does and reflecting the practices outlined here.

## Information security and quality

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.

## Business relationships

The YONEX site may contain links to other websites. YONEX is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

## Cookies

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some YONEX pages use cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

## Questions? Please Contact Us:

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, you can contact us.
